A story behind one of the most influential shows of all time.
Being the Ricardos is a drama, history film directed by Aaron Sorkin.
Lucille Ball and Desi Arnaz face a crisis that could end their
careers and another that could end their marriage.
Lucille Ball, played by Nicole Kidman.
Desi Arnaz, played by Javier Bardem.
William Frawley, played by J.K. Simmons.
Vivian Vance, played by Nina Arianda.
Jess Oppenheimer, played by Tony Hale.
Madelyn Pugh, played by Alia Shawkat.
Being the Ricardos is a 2021 American biographical drama film written and directed by Aaron
Sorkin, about the relationship between I Love Lucy stars Lucille Ball and Desi Arnaz.
Nicole Kidman and Javier Bardem star as Ball and Arnaz, while J.
Simmons, Nina Arianda, Tony Hale, Alia Shawkat, Jake Lacy, and
Clark Gregg are featured in supporting roles.
It received a limited theatrical release by Amazon Studios in the United States on December
10, 2021, prior to streaming worldwide on Prime Video on December 21, 2021.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics who praised the
performances of the cast, particularly those of Kidman and Bardem.
The film received three nominations at the 94th Academy Awards: Best Actor for
Bardem, Best Actress for Kidman and Best Supporting Actor for Simmons.
It also received three nominations at the 79th Golden Globe Awards including Best Actor – Motion Picture Drama for
Bardem and Best Screenplay for Sorkin, with Kidman winning Best Actress – Motion Picture Drama.
The film explores themes of show business, marriage,
biography, based on true story, interracial marriage.
The tone is emotional.